#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vy-nguyen-b18a5622a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Usability Testing
Mobile Design
Web Design

# Vy Nguyen

**UI/UX** Designer

Da Nang City, Vietnam

#### Summary

A UX/UI Designer with a passion for crafting intuitive digital experiences that support tasks for users while driving optimal project outcomes.

Proficient in management system design in Web & Mobile applications. Embracing a commitment to continuous learning and knowledge-sharing as core values.

## Experience

DataHouse Asia
UI/UX Designer
March 2022 - Present (3 years 1 month)

Nestsera Technology
UI/UX Intern
September 2021 - December 2021 (4 months)
Da Nang City, Vietnam

## Education

The Interaction Design Foundation

Mobile UI Design · (March 2024 - April 2024)

#### Coursera

Google Google UX Design Professional Certificate, UX Design · (August 2022 - August 2023)

University of Economics - The University of Danang
Bachelor's Degree in International Business, International Business · (May 2014 - June 2018)